all stores
online should
copy the strategy you are using from pet Lab co
because the truth is that he is breaking it
and they can't believe how many ads they have running around
and how to explain
its products
it's the best I saw far away they have dog products
that are fundamental
explain what it is and show the details
and have fixed
this publication
as it also shows
all the benefits and features of the product
and before and after that it's okay
and this is something we repeat
to each of our customers
to iterate over their organic content
as inorganic
I'm going to show you now because it's crazy.
look at the amount of content
citario that they have guidelines
is crazy
say okay good Nico but how is the landing good
look at the landing
because all the advertising content is derived here from
look at all the details
explained products collected testimonials
whose came
i.e.
all verifications to be able to generate
trust in its customers is focused on landing and it is
all the time
I say the same
the weakest point of an online business is to generate
confidence and attract customers
then when you start attracting customers
you need to build trust so that you can be paid
you always have to think that you are at a
as if it were a stained glass window
but online people can't
grab the product,
test the product and so on
all he has is too much confidence
people who have tried it
that is to say,
the humble ones are basically testimonies
variation that may be,
for example,
approval in Argentina.
the clearest example is that it has the ANMAT insignia
or a lot of things
eh I'm just talking about consumable products em
I don't know about products
of all types eh can be supplements etc.
in this case
but then in other areas that this applies to all areas.
is to generate
confidence so if you liked this video save it because
nothing probably
you need some of what I said and follow me
because I help brands to load their turnover and contribute a lot of
value in TikTok I upload all the
days videos I'm a gede but I love what I do.
so eh nothing follow me for more